let's look at the answer to our atomic
instruction quiz which asks what do we
need to implement locks easily an
instruction that loads memory stores to
memory or one that reads and writes
memory or one that doesn't access memory
at all we already saw that we need an
instruction that does something like
this without interference from others so
we need an instruction that atomically
does these two operations one is a read
one is a write so an instruction that
just reads memory will not give us what
we want it's capable of doing this but
it's not going to let us do this a store
might be able to do this but it cannot
first check the lock variable to see
whether it's available so what we need
really is an instruction that both reads
and then writes memory and certainly we
don't need an instruction that doesn't
access memory because the lock bar is a
memory location so the correct answer is
this